[Music]
every two seconds a person is forced to
flee every day forty-four thousand four
hundred more are driven from their homes
at the end of 2017 that total reached
sixty eight point five million a new
record children men and women escaping
violence and persecution and searching
for safety these are lives not numbers
the lives of people who pay the price of
a world in conflict twenty five point
four million refugees among them nearly
three million more than in 2016 they
have fled across borders leaving their
country behind Mambazo cetera ba o
ReadySet Montella sits on table visca
apprentice at monte isola bella yap a
deaf person so to party a guru an
additional 40 million are displaced
inside their own country I've seen any
caboose help this need a harness
[Music]
over two-thirds of the world's refugees
come from just five countries Syria
Afghanistan South Sudan Myanmar
Somalia
some of these conflicts have dragged on
for years others have flared recently
with dramatic consequences
last year deadly violence in Myanmar
triggered the exodus of nearly 700,000
row Hingis who crossed into Bangladesh
in just a few months answer my located
within myself first of I'm at the
Messiah speculum area for d'Ivoire the
bottom on the very first rather than
wanna miss Akane - no moola pasola
suppose I did the first radical a know
that Mogadishu calamari I see the
current behind the numbers lie
individual hopes and hardships not just
of the displaced but also of those who
host them these Congolese children lost
their parents in an attack and managed
to flee they walked for more than two
weeks before Papa Shah and his wife with
ten children of their own took them in
Namibia can't a list of T poor shipshape
and then we clear por la famille
allotropy
citizen father Banda Neira mm / PG ELISA
Romani already know who some zbg a a
perilous offer on a continued have a
lizard sacrifice Milani
[Music]
most displaced people live in or close
to the world's conflict zones so just a
handful of countries host the largest
refugee populations turkey Pakistan
[Music]
Uganda Lebanon and Iran with forced
displacement at a record high for the
fifth consecutive year a new approach to
aiding and protecting refugees is needed
now more than ever
United Nations member states have
committed to work towards a global
compact on refugees the compact will
come before the UN General Assembly this
year it is a vital way forward it starts
from a hard truth that refugee
situations will exist as long as Wars do
and that it may take years before
refugees can safely return home it calls
for action from across the international
community
and it allows us to harness ideas and
innovations from new partners from the
development world to the private sector
who all become part of the solution
this approach prioritizes education the
millions of displaced children and work
for their parents every day brings proof
that their inclusion in host societies
benefits all that asylum is a critical
solution which saves lives and that the
power of the human spirit can bridge
cultural divides one in every 110 people
on earth is now forcibly displaced
we know the only lasting solution for
them is peace but with solidarity
resilience and ingenuity we are building
a better way forward together
you